

CONTACT

- Skopje, North Macedonia
- +38971227094
- kika.max57@outlook.com

PROFILE

Highly resourceful, proficient and results driven IT professional offering extensive experience in planning, implementing, supporting and maintaining complex IT infrastructures. Technical and customer support agent with more than 4 years experience in telephone customer service, sales, tech support, recruiting new employees. Familiar with handling, and configuration fixing issues. Constantly evolving and growing. Positive, hard worker with a lot of patience.

№ LANGUAGES

Macedonian - Native Serbo-Croatian - Advanced English - Advanced Spanish - Upper Intermediate French - Basic

HRISTINA NIKOLOVA

MANAGER IN TELECOMMUNICATIONS

EDUCATION

Military Academy General "Mihailo Apostolski", Skopje, Republic of North Macedonia - Branch Signal Corps

Norwich University, Senior Military College, Vermont, USA (4 months study porgram) January - May 2019

Major in telecommunications management Graduated Summa Cum Laude

Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering

Master in Security, Cryptography & Coding 2022 - Present

CYBERWISER (learning platform)

PRIMER Cybersecurity course
BASIC Cybersecurity course
INTERMEDIATE Cybersecurity course
ADVANCED Cybersecurity course
CISCO Packet Tracer courses
2020/2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

Army of the Republic of North Macedonia -Signal Battalion, Company for stationary communication information centers

Commander of a Platoon: December 2021 - present

- Includes people management
- Organising activities and events
- Being responsible for 30 people (or sometimes 60 people)
- Operating and setting up IP telephony, alongside the NCOs and soldiers
- Looking after all the activities connected with setting up optical cables, troubleshooting, telephony, static telephones
- Observe, evaluate and make soldiers progress

INTERSPACE: May 2019 - August 2020 (1.3 years)

Customer and technical support agent

- Answering large volume of technical support tickets
- Rerouting calls through different networks
- Maintained up to date knowledge of products and services
- Handled customer calls with patience and responded to queries about services, malfunctions
- Oversee infrastructure engineering and support
- Maintained and managed IT inventory including
- Accountable for providing moderate to complex technical support to end users via email, phone or other devices on problems related to hardware, software or connectivity issues
- Maximised efficiency by consistently troubleshooting network performance issues and recommending best solutions

The Group: September 2020 - November 2021 (1.1 year)

Assistant Recruiter

- Writing job ads and description
- Posting job ads
- Contacting potential applicants
- Scheduling interviews with candidates applicants
- Following up during the recruitment process
- Updating employee records

T-Mobile: January 2017 - February 2019 (2.1 years)

Customer service representative

- Handling 50-60 customer tickets daily
- Responding to customers emails effectively
- Maintained up to date knowledge of products and services
- Carefully followed established procedures to ensure customers get the correct information and a speedy resolution to their issue
- Prioritised tickets based on what is in the inbox that day
- Collaborated with design, operations or tech when something wasn't working or was not looking incorrect

⟨♥ SKILLS

- Client Relationship Management
- Troubleshooting Techniques
- Conflict Resolution
- Complex Problem Solving
- Analytical and Critical Thinking
- Technical Research and Analysis
- Phone, Email and Chat Technical support
- Multitasking

TOOLS

- Microsoft Office
- AutoCAD
- Adobe Photoshop
- Cisco Packet Tracer
- Salesforce Customer 360
- Slack
- Zendesk
- HubSpot Service Hub
- Broadvoice